Skate Steps
It's before the third show of the spring tour!
Well, the Sendai show, or rather the Miyagi show.
We've already finished two shows in Sendai or Miyagi, and they were great shows.
I'd like to show you even better live performance.
And this tour...
I can see that you put a lot of emphasis on the story.
I hope you will pay attention to that.
I'm going to come to you all.
I hope I can communicate with you there.
I will do my best.
Now, you are going to perform in Saitama today.
Yes, we still have Sendai and the other day, and we are still in the first half of the second year.
And we are still in the first half of our second year.
I'm going to do my best.
The highlight in my opinion is
Appearance and waveforms
I would like you to see the appearance and the waveforms.
If you come to the show, you can definitely see it.
I hope you're looking forward to it!
Well then, I'll do my best at the rehearsal!
Good morning.
You can take a video with this.
My mom gave me her camera.
I brought it today.
I'll try.
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning. I'm KMJP.
Let's have a good rehearsal.
Thank you very much.
Okay, let's go to rehearsal.
Yes, please come to the rehearsal.
Thank you very much for the rehearsal.
Please take care of the Saitama performance.
Thank you very much.
Hello, I'm Sakurame, a user.
So, today I'll be talking about
I'll be at the imaginary outline of Saitama Park. This is a fictitious outline Saitama Park!
It's the second park, the third park, but it's actually
It's the second place, spring tour
I'm really looking forward to this spring tour.
I'm really looking forward to this tour with a fresh feeling.
It's a live show that makes me realize how wonderful it is to meet new people.
I feel like I've never seen the expressions on the audience's faces when they see me perform live.
I felt like I saw expressions on the audience's faces that I've never seen before.
I think that's one of the advantages of the spring tour.
I think that's one of the good points of the spring tour.
Today's show is in Saitama.
We don't have a show in Tokyo this time, so we are performing in Saitama in the Kanto area.
I really hope to share a good time with all the observers who gathered in Saitama.
I hope we can share a good time with all the observers who gathered in Saitama.
And more than anything else, this time
I hope to share a good time with all the observers who gathered in Saitama.
I hope to deliver the story to all of you.
I hope you will join in the story and feel the reality at the end.
And at the end of the show, you will end up feeling the reality of the story.
I hope we can make it such a live performance
I'm looking forward to it.
Among the songs, I especially like
Before the song "Diamond Lily
Before the song "Diamond Lily", there is an interlude.
It's like half a play, so please pay attention to it.
I hope you will pay attention to it.
I'll do my best for the Saitama performance.
The game is in my hands, and it's a no-brainer.
It is the Saitama performance of the spring tour, isn't it?
Imaginary outline
Rehearsal has just finished.
After this, we'll go on stage.
Well, it's the spring tour this time.
It's kind of a spring tour.
We've prepared a medley of songs that are appropriate for spring.
A medley of songs
We are going to make a story with new songs of concept EP. Creating a story with new songs from the concept EP.
This live performance is full of such highlights!
For me, I think it's a good idea
In the middle of the show.
In the middle of the show, they give the impression that the show is about to end...
And then they say, "No, we're still going to do it.
I really recommend the flow from there.
I'll do my best for the live performance after this.
I look forward to working with you.
My name is Ryota Nagano.
I'm Ryota Nagano and this is the second or third show of the live tour 2024 Fictitious Outline.
We did two shows in Sendai last time, and today we're going to Saitama.
I'm always nervous at every show, but I'm just as nervous every time.
Ryota Nagano is always nervous, but this spring tour is different.
This spring tour is different from usual, there's no encore and only one MC.
It's a pretty aggressive set list.
Entrance? The entrance? The beginning of the show?
The beginning of the show was like a barrage of smoke, and then the band members came on stage without being seen.
When you exhale, it's also a bar of smoke.
This show is based on a concept EP, so it's a storybook show.
I was wondering if there was a connection between these parts and the story.
or "Maybe this part is connected to that part," or "Maybe this story is connected to that part..." and so on.
I think it's a show that you can enjoy no matter how many times you come.
If you come this time, I'm sure you'll be happy to see the making of the show.
I'd be happy if you could think of such things that happened in the past, along with the making of the show.
I'm so nervous because the show is almost here.
I'm going to do my best today.
I'm off!
Hello everyone, this is Takato Okura.
Today is the Saitama concert!
This time, we're going to perform the concept EP, "You, the Family Lawyer," for our spring tour, "Fictitious Outline.
It's the Saitama show this time.
All the performances are like a story in the 6 songs of the concept EP.
It's like a story.
This song, the worldview changes so many times.
And the way it ends... it has a very fantastic and ephemeral ending.
It's one of my main points of interest.
I think it's important to have a song with a key point before the song.Before a certain song, I do a ballet dance by myself.
Before a certain song, Kaname does a ballet dance by himself.
As a member of the group, I felt that Kaname's ballet skills
I felt like the time had finally come for me to live up to it.
I've been watching every performance with trembling heart and excitement.
I hope you all will pay attention to it.
I'll do my best for the Saitama performance.
Today is the performance in Saitama.
I'm really fired up for it.
I'm really fired up!
This tour is very much based on the story.
It's like watching a show on stage.
It's really hard to concentrate.
I'm going to do my best.
The best part of the show for me is...
Masaya and I are dancing together.
The best part of the show for me is... dancing with Masaya.
The best part for me is that Masaya and I dance together.
We have a weapon block, and that's the highlight of the show.
The two youngest dancers dancing together is very emo.
That's the highlight.
I'll do my best.
See you soon!
The show is about to start!
Well, it's a little bit...
I'm a little nervous for this exquisitely long time.
I'll do my best.
I've noticed something.
When you're nervous, your breathing becomes shallow.
If you take deep breaths, you'll calm down.
I can't calm down at all.
Yes, sir.
You're flabby.
Thank you for watching.
So, the Saitama concert is over!
It's over!
How was it?
It was great! Oh, no.
You ate.
Hey...
As you can see, I'm exhausted.
We've done it!
Observers in Saitama were really energetic!
You know...
They were so energetic.
We were so energized, too, and that's why, as Jun said...
So we decided to do it even more.
That's right.
We were able to give it our all.
It was a clash of firepower with firepower.
Well, it really was.
Well, it's a fun tour, really.
Yeah.
I think we've got four more shows, including the next one, three?
Three?
Four?
4?
I only have 4, right?
Yes, Fukuoka, Osaka, Osaka.
It's not that there are 4 times, it's just that I feel like there are only 4 times.
I'm going to make the most of each one and do my best again.
I will do my best again.
Well, Masaya, please give us your closing comment.
Well, I really want to do the next one in, let's see, where is the next one?
Not Fukuoka.
Fukuoka.
Yes, the next one is in Aichi. Aichi.
I'm looking forward to seeing you all next time in Aichi.
See you soon.
Bye bye!
Bye bye! radius